<resources>
    <!-- Formato de comentario -->
    <string name="app_name">FreeToFeel</string>

    <!-- LoginBase -->
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome</string>
    <string name="login_text">Login</string>
    <string name="new_account_text">Sign up</string>

    <!-- New Account -->
    <string name="new_account_welcome1">Time to start</string>
    <string name="new_account_welcome2">again</string>
    <string name="OTF_user">Register your username</string>
    <string name="OTF_email">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="OTF_password1">Enter your password</string>
    <string name="OTF_password2">Confirm your password</string>
    <string name="CreateAcc">Create account</string>

    <!-- FirstPet -->
    <string name="first_pet_title">Welcome to this exciting adventure!</string>
    <string name="first_pet_body1">I’m Sun, the guardian of this universe full of harmony and calm. Recently, four little inhabitants have been facing challenges and feeling down. Would you join me in bringing joy back to their lives and lighting up their worlds? Together, we can make a difference. </string>
    <string name="first_pet_body2">Could you join me in lending them a hand and bringing their happiness back? I am sure that, with your help, we will brighten their worlds once again!</string>
    <string name="first_pet_confirm">Sure!</string>

    <!-- PetTalk -->
    <string name="pet_talk_title1">I really panicked!</string>
    <string name="pet_talk_body1">I went out to buy some flowers to decorate my house, but there was a lot of people in the store! I panicked a bit, and I just wanted to run away, but, just as you have taught me, I kept my calm and actually bought them. </string>
    <string name="pet_talk_option1A">You should have ran away</string>
    <string name="pet_talk_option1B">At least you\'re not there anymore</string>
    <string name="pet_talk_option1C">You\'re so brave! You\'ll see next time will be better</string> <!-- Posiblemente intentar que siempre la C sea la correcta, e ir variando la posicion ya dentro de los buttons con un random)? -->

    <!-- PetTalk -->
    <string name="pet_lazy_title1">Just someone around…</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_body1">Oh, hi. I haven’t seen you over here. Are you new around? This is a nice place, there are so many special things… How I wish I could be as special… Well, whatever, since you just arrived, why don’t you visit the Sun? You will get along.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option1A">Thanks for the welcome.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option1B">Ehh, thanks?</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option1C">Nice to meet you!</string>

    <string name="pet_lazy_title2">Oh, you’re here again. Have you found someone special yet? You know, someone who can fly, swim, run, do something… more than just lying down doing… nothing. I think I am sleepy… yeah, I shall better just sleep, I don’t feel like doing something.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_body2">Yes, I’ve already found others happier than you.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option2A">Yes, I’ve already found others happier than you.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option2B">Lying down all day is also a cool activity.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option2C">Hey, cheer up a bit. You are also special!</string>

    <string name="pet_lazy_title3">Perhaps?</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_body3">Hi again. I’m aware it may not concern you, but I’ve been more reflective since you arrived, you know? Tell me, do you really think that I could be interesting? I mean, I know I don’t do extraordinary actions, but… isn’t that exactly what defines me as I am?</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option3A">Look, I really don’t care.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option3B">Yeah, you are kind of right.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option3C">Nice! You finally got it!</string>

    <string name="pet_lazy_title4">Good news</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_body4">Look at me! I Managed to climb more than 5 trees today! I’m usually only able to climb 2, because I looked at how others could climb faster than me, and that turned me sad, because I couldn’t. But today I told myself that I was doing it my way, even if that took a long time. And this is the result!</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option4A">You took long as well…</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option4B">Good one, congratulations.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option4C">I feel happy for you!</string>

    <string name="pet_lazy_title5">A reason to smile</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_body5">Today I didn’t climb 5 trees, I tried to swim! And you know what I did after that? Sleep, sleep and sleep; with one single difference: for the first time, I didn’t feel bad doing it. I just needed to accept that sleeping a lot is part of me, but I’m not condemned to do only that. Of course, I take a long time to do other stuff, but that doesn’t mean I won’t try. Thanks to you, I had the confidence to keep trying.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option5A">You are welcome.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option5B">I’ll always be there for you.</string>
    <string name="pet_lazy_option5C">I’m happy to hear that, friend.</string>


    <!-- erizo -->
    <string name="pet_hedge_title1">A little stumble</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_body1">Oh, I’m sorry… did I hurt you? I didn’t notice you were by my side. I’m so sorry! Oh, no… it happened again! I’m truly sorry… I don’t get along with people, and on top of that I even bump with them without noticing… Oh, no… I’m not made for this…</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option1A">You should look around more carefully</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option1B">It’s alright.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option1C">I’m sorry as well. Are you ok?</string>

    <string name="pet_hedge_title2">Intrusive thoughts</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_body2">Oh, no, it’s you again… Are you here to complain about last time? I knew it! I knew you would hate me. I told you it wasn’t my fault. I spend all this time thinking about how much would you hate me, and planning something bad to do to me… I am truly sorry; it was not my intention, so please don’t hurt me, nor yell at me, nor hate me, ok?</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option2A">But what are you talking about!?</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option2B">It’s fine.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option2C">Don’t worry, everything is fine.</string>

    <string name="pet_hedge_title3">You still here</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_body3">Oh, is that… you? Why do you keep talking to me? Usually, most people just stop talking to me, and end up hating me; why don’t you? Perhaps… do you like me? Do you really like me? This is… incredible! Thanks, I really don’t know what to say.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option3A">Don’t assume it right away.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option3B">You are welcome.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option3C">Yes, I like you!</string>

    <string name="pet_hedge_title4">A question in mind</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_body4">Hey, um… I have a question: do you think that I can be liked by other people as well? I mean, if I could do so once, I could also do it another time, right? It is… that I want to talk with more people. I’ve never wanted to! but since you came, that mentality has changed.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option4A">If I were you, I wouldn’t try.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option4B">It could be.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option4C">Of course! You completely can.</string>

    <string name="pet_hedge_title5">A new friend</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_body5">I have something to tell you! I met someone else, now he’s my friend! I spoke to him after thinking about what I told you last time. It turns out that he is also trying new things, and meeting someone is one of them. We get along well! Thank you, because without you I would not have dared to talk to him.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option5A">You’re welcome.</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option5B">I’m very happy to hear it!</string>
    <string name="pet_hedge_option5C">Keep making many more friends!</string>



    <!-- bee -->
    <string name="pet_bee_title1">Wasting the time</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_body1">Hey, excuse me, could you move please? You are right in front of my recollection flower number 455 of today. If I don’t recollect that flower, then I will be delayed with 456 and 457, in summary, a complete disaster. Well, you delayed me more than my 5 seconds to rest; so please move.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option1A">So rude.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option1B">I didn’t know, sorry.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option1C">Don’t worry, I’ll help you.</string>

    <string name="pet_bee_title2">Do you ever do something?</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_body2">Hey, you again, standing in front of the same flower. Could you move? I never see you doing something productive, do you ever do something? Haven’t you considered that you waste so much your time? All the time you spend standing in front of flowers is time you could be working, are you aware?</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option2A">And what does that concern you?</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option2B">But I’m doing something!</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option2C">For your health, you should rest.</string>

    <string name="pet_bee_title3">For the first time…</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_body3">Oh…Hey. Hm? Why I’m not working with my flowers? Well, something weird happened… I felt tired. For the first time in my life, I felt fatigue… How horrible it feels! I barely have enough energy to fly… I don’t know how I manage to accomplish my 999 flower fee.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option3A">You deserved it.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option3B">Rest a bit and then you continue.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option3C">It’s a signal to stop.</string>

    <string name="pet_bee_title4">… I smelled a flower.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_body4">Oh, hi! Do you know the scent of flowers? I know it will sound odd, but today was the first day that I smelled a flower. I’ve always worked with them, but I actually never stopped to smell one of them. I always told myself that I didn’t have time to do so… was that true?</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option4A">You discovered your nose!</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option4B">Flowers are cute.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option4C">I’m glad that you took the time.</string>

    <string name="pet_bee_title5">Just 10 of them</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_body5">Hello, do you want a flower? I’m giving the ones I’m collecting. You know? I discovered that I only need 10 flowers per day to survive, and not 999. Then, I’m flying around, collecting them, smelling them, and giving them to the others, it’s funnier that way! By the way, I wanted to thank you. Without you, I wouldn’t have taken the time to…do all of this.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option5A">You are welcome.</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option5B">I accept the flower!</string>
    <string name="pet_bee_option5C">Keep giving them to others!</string>


    <!-- jelly -->
    <string name="pet_jelly_title1">Painful solitude</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_body1">Hello, I haven’t seen you around here. What’s your name? Well, you’ll leave soon too, as everything always leave… It hurts to be left alone, don’t you think? It hurts wanting to have the people you love around all the time, but they just… leave.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option1A">I may also leave.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option1B">Hey, don’t be so sad.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option1C">Something I can support?</string>

    <string name="pet_jelly_title2">An endless life</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_body2">Hey, do you have friends? It’s just that mine’s… Well, it doesn’t matter. May I tell you something curious? I live forever. I can’t die, at least, for ageing. I know it may be something that others would like but living it is not enjoyable. All people leave and you just stay… alone.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option2A">I wish I were immortal.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option2B">Nice curious fact</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option2C">With me, you’re not alone.</string>

    <string name="pet_jelly_title3">The friends I had</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_body3">I don’t like living forever. Lately, all my friends have died; I really loved them. I remember them very often… and cry a lot when that happens. When will this suffering end? When will I be able to be happy again? When will I stop remembering them?</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option3A">…</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option3B">I feel sorry.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option3C">I am here for you.</string>

    <string name="pet_jelly_title4">It’s fine to cry</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_body4">Recently I kept remembering my friends. I cried a lot again… and suddenly I calmed down.  The sorrow was still there, of course, but it wasn’t as strong as at the beginning. I thought that crying was bad, but I think it’s helping me. I also think that remembering them is fine.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option4A">Crying is bad.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option4B">You’re on a good way.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option4C">There’s a lesson everywhere.</string>

    <string name="pet_jelly_title5">The way forward</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_body5">Yesterday I visited my friends’ families. I cried a bit and felt better. I think that’s the way to go: to keep forward, remembering the ones that left. And even if sometimes I feel alone, to remember that there’s always someone who loves me, or loved me.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option5A">Good decision.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option5B">I’m glad to hear that.</string>
    <string name="pet_jelly_option5C">You are never alone.</string>

    <!--LoginInput -->
    <string name="login_input_title1">Nice to have you</string>
    <string name="login_input_title2">back</string>
    <string name="LI_email">Enter your email</string>
    <string name="login_button">Login</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">I forgot my password</string>

    <!-- PetHome -->
    <string name="pet_home_button1">Tip of the day</string>
    <string name="pet_home_button2">History</string>
    <string name="points">Points</string>

    <!-- PetSelect -->
    <string name="pet_select_topAppBar">Creatures</string>
    <string name="pet_select_mainMSG">Choose a friend</string>
    <string name="pet_select_sloth">Mimioso</string>
    <string name="pet_select_sloth_problem">Depression</string>
    <string name="pet_select_hedgehog_problem">Social anxiety</string>
    <string name="pet_select_bee_problem">Workaholic</string>
    <string name="pet_select_jelly_problem">Mourning</string>

    <!-- DailyReco -->
    <string name="dailyreco_val_completed">Filled!</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_view">Accept</string>

    <!-- Retos -->
    <string name="dailyreco_title_example">Tip of the day</string>
    <string name="dialyreco_text_example">Take care of the Earth! There ane more then 1.5 million species on Earth; each one is worth it. Get out of your room and water a plant, feed an animal or, why not, give something to someone as a gift; This way you will value their lives!</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title1">Listen to your emotions</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text1">Today, take the time to observe how you’re feeling without judging yourself. If you’re feeling sad, allow that emotion to exist without trying to change it. Write it down in a journal, draw how you feel, or simply sit in silence. Remember that all emotions are valid, and understanding them will make you stronger.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title2">Do something kind for a stranger</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text2">Go out with a purpose: do something kind for someone you don’t know. It could be helping someone cross the street, paying for a stranger’s coffee, or simply smiling at someone who seems to be having a bad day. You’ll see how a small gesture can transform someone else’s day.\.. and yours too! </string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title3">Disconnect to reconnect</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text3">Dedicate the whole day to staying away from screens. Put your phone away, turn off the TV, and find creative ways to spend your time: cook a new recipe, paint, organize your home, or explore a park. Discover how being present in the moment can enrich your day.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title4">Plan a special moment</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text4">Plan a simple but meaningful gesture for someone you love. It could be preparing a special dinner, planning a game night, or writing a list of reasons why you appreciate that person. This gesture will not only strengthen your bond but also make you feel more connected.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title5">Transform a fear</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text5">Reflect on a fear you have and write down how you would face it if it didn’t hold you back. Then, take a small step toward overcoming it, such as researching it or talking to someone you trust. Facing your fears in small steps can be a big leap for your personal growth.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title6">Turn your day into art</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text6">Use any form of artistic expression to capture your day. You can write a poem, draw, create a song, or take photographs that represent how you feel. You don’t need to be an expert; the important thing is to express your essence through art.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title7">Choose a small goal</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text7">Think of a goal you’ve always wanted to achieve but feel is too far away. Today, create a small and realistic plan to start. Break the goal into simple steps and complete the first one. Remember: every big achievement starts with a small step.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title8">Change your perspective</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text8">Spend 10 minutes looking at a situation from a different perspective. If something bothers or worries you, imagine how someone else would see it. This exercise can help you develop empathy and understand that things aren’t always what they seem.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title9">Celebrate your progress</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text9">Make a list of moments when you’ve overcome difficulties in the past. Acknowledge the effort you put in and how far you’ve come. Remember that you have the strength to overcome any challenge you face today.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title10">A complaint-free day</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text10">Commit to going the entire day without complaining. Instead of focusing on the negative, look for something positive in every situation. This exercise can change how you perceive your day and increase your gratitude.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title11">Connect with yourself</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text11">Spend 10 minutes today meditating. Find a quiet and comfortable spot, close your eyes, and take deep breaths. Focus on the rhythm of your breathing, allowing your thoughts to flow without judging or clinging to them. This is a moment to reconnect with yourself and calm your mind. By the end, you\'ll feel more relaxed and at peace!</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title12">Gratitude day</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text12">Take a moment to write down three things you’re grateful for today. It doesn’t matter if they’re small, like enjoying a warm cup of coffee, or big, like the company of a loved one. What matters is focusing on the positive and letting that gratitude brighten your day.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title13">Write a letter</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text13">Today, write a letter to someone important to you. It could be a friend you miss, a family member you love, or even your future self. Write from the heart, expressing your thoughts, emotions, and wishes. Sometimes, putting your feelings into words can be deeply liberating.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title14">Offline moment</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text14">Disconnect from social media for an hour today. Use this time to reconnect with yourself or do something you genuinely enjoy. It could be reading a book, painting, cooking your favorite dish, or simply enjoying a quiet walk. You’ll be surprised at how refreshing it can be!</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title15">Listen to someone</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text15">Ask a friend, colleague, or loved one about their day. Listen attentively, setting aside distractions, and let them know you genuinely care about what they share. Being a good listener can strengthen bonds and bring joy to both of you.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title16">Mindful steps</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text16">Take a walk, but this time do it with full awareness. Feel the ground beneath your feet, listen to the sound of your footsteps, and observe the small details around you: the colors, the sounds, the air on your face. This exercise will help you live in the present moment.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title17">Complete a small goal </string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text17">Today, choose a task you’ve been putting off and finish it. It could be something simple like organizing a drawer, planting a flower, or replying to a message. Completing small goals brings great satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title18">Unexpected gift </string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text18">Give someone a small token for no reason at all. It could be a compliment, a handwritten note, or even a simple "thank you." Spontaneous gestures have the power to brighten any day.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title19">The art of breathing</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text19">Practice the 4\-7\-8 breathing technique: inhale for 4 seconds, hold for 7, and exhale for 8. It’s a simple but effective method to reduce anxiety and improve your overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title20">Reconnect moment</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text20">Call a friend or family member you haven’t spoken to in a while. Take a few minutes to remind them how much you value their friendship and how much they mean to you.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title21">Care for your space</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text21">Pick a small area in your home and tidy or clean it up. It could be your desk, a shelf, or your nightstand. An organized environment can work wonders for your mental clarity.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title22">Healthy challenge</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text22">Make the effort to drink an extra glass of water today. Staying hydrated boosts your energy, focus, and overall health. Your body and mind will thank you!</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title23">Celebrate your wins</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text23">Reflect on your accomplishments this week, big or small. Recognizing your progress strengthens your confidence and motivates you to keep going.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title24">Learn something new</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text24">Spend 10 minutes researching an interesting topic or practicing a new skill. Expanding your horizons is always rewarding.</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_title25">Share a compliment</string>
    <string name="dailyreco_text25">Find something you admire in someone and let them know. It could be their smile, their positive attitude, or something they did. A compliment can make their day brighter.</string>


    <!-- PetEvolved -->
    <string name="pet_evolved_topAppBar">Evolutions</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_baseSloth">Normal sloth</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_evoSloth">Evolved sloth</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_baseBee">Normal bee</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_evoBee">Evolved bee</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_baseHedgehog">Normal hedgehog</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_evoHedgehog">Evolved hedgehog</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_baseJelly">Normal jellyfish</string>
    <string name="pet_evolved_evoJelly">Evolved jellyfish</string>

    <!-- ProfileHome -->
    <string name="profile_home_greeting">Hello!</string>
    <string name="profile_home_points">Points</string>
    <string name="profile_home_days">Days</string>
    <string name="profile_home_tips">Tips and challenges</string>
    <string name="profile_home_iLike">I like</string>
    <string name="profile_home_iDisLike">I dislike</string>
    <string name="profile_home_aboutMe">About me</string>
    <string name="profile_home_myWritings">My writings</string>
    <string name="profile_home_viewB">View</string>
    <string name="profile_home_editB">Edit</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>

    <!-- Sun Feeling -->
    <string name="sunFeeling_ask">how do you feel today?</string>
    <string name="sunFeeling_happy">Happy</string>
    <string name="sunFeeling_restless">Restless</string>
    <string name="sunFeeling_sad">Sad</string>
    <string name="sunFeeling_angry">Angry</string>
    <string name="sunFeeling_bored">Bored</string>

    <!-- SunHome -->
    <string name="sun_home_question">do you need something?</string>
    <string name="sun_home_buttonA">Express an emotion</string>
    <string name="sun_home_buttonB">Describe my day</string>
    <string name="sun_home_buttonC">Tell something about me</string>

    <!-- Sun Talk -->
    <string name="sunTalk_example_title">Oh, something bad happened?</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_example_text">No Problem, you learn from everything, and everything happens for a reason. Let that emotion flow, but do not let it hurt others, okay?</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_button">Okay!</string>

    <!-- Sun Talk Sad -->
    <string name="sunTalk_sad1_title">I\'m sorry to hear you are sad</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad1_body">Try to distract from what\'s making you sad. Breathe slowly and think of what makes you happy.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad2_title">Feeling down?</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad2_body">It\'s okay to feel sad sometimes. Let yourself process the emotion, and remember brighter days are ahead.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad3_title">You\'re not alone</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad3_body">Even in sadness, there\'s strength. Reach out to someone who cares; you\'re never alone in this.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad4_title">A cloudy moment?</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad4_body">Clouds may cover the sun, but it’s still shining behind them. Your light is waiting to shine again!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad5_title">This, too, shall pass</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad5_body">Every feeling is temporary. Give yourself time and kindness; you’ll feel better soon.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad6_title">Take a deep breath</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad6_body">Sometimes all it takes is a moment to pause, breathe, and let the sadness settle.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad7_title">You are stronger than you think</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad7_body">Sadness shows you are human, it’s normal to feel so. You can overcome this.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad8_title">It’s okay to cry</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad8_body">Tears are how the heart speaks when words cannot. Let them flow; they heal.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad9_title">Find the lesson</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad9_body">Even in sadness, life teaches us something valuable. Look for the lesson; it’s always there.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad10_title">You deserve kindness</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad10_body">Be gentle with yourself. Sadness is tough, but you deserve care and love, always.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad11_title">A new day awaits</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad11_body">Today may feel heavy, but tomorrow always brings new hope.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad12_title">Embrace your humanity</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad12_body">Sadness is part of the human being. It means you care deeply, and that’s beautiful.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad13_title">You’re enough</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad13_body">Even in sadness, you’re whole, worthy, and enough. Don’t let this sadness consume you.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad14_title">You’re healing</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_sad14_body">Every tear, every cry, is a step toward healing. Trust the process.</string>


    <!-- Sun Talk Angry -->
    <string name="sunTalk_angry1_title">It\'s OK to be angry</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry1_body">Just do not hurt other people while doing so. Relax listening to music and let your mind blow off the anger.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry2_title">Everything will be fine</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry2_body">Whatever made you angry will eventually stop. Don\'t waste your time my being angry, while you can be feeling in peace.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry3_title">Take a deep breath</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry3_body">Anger can cloud your thoughts. Breathe deeply, and let your emotions settle before acting.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry4_title">Hold on, it’s temporary</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry4_body">Anger is fleeting. Don’t let it define your day or your actions.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry5_title">Let it go</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry5_body">Holding onto anger only weighs you down. Release it for your own peace.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry6_title">Smile through it</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry6_body">A smile can help you break the anger cycle. Try it.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry7_title">You’re in control</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry7_body">Anger doesn’t control you unless you let it. You have the power to choose calm.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry8_title">Channel your energy</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry8_body">Anger is energy. Use it to build something, not destroy.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry9_title">Think about tomorrow</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry9_body">How you handle this moment will shape how you feel tomorrow. Think forwards.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry10_title">Take a walk</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry10_body">Sometimes, stepping away is the best way to step forward. Take a breath.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry11_title">Focus on solutions</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry11_body">Shift from the problem to the solution. Anger won’t fix what’s wrong.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry12_title">Pause, don’t react</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry12_body">Reacting in anger rarely helps. Pause, think clearly, and respond with a cool mind.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry13_title">Find perspective</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry13_body">Will this matter in a week, a month, or a year? Keep the big picture in mind.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry14_title">Anger is a teacher</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry14_body">Anger highlights what matters to you. Learn from it without letting it take over.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry15_title">It’s okay to feel</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry15_body">Anger is normal. Allow yourself to feel it, but don’t let it control you.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry16_title">Anger fades, memories stay</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_angry16_body">Don’t let anger create moments you’ll regret. Act with kindness.</string>

    <!-- Sun Talk bored -->
    <string name="sunTalk_bored1_title">Time for something new!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored1_body">Boredom is a sign you’re ready for a new adventure. Try something you’ve never done before!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored2_title">Create your own fun</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored2_body">What’s something you can create or build right now? Fun starts with you!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored3_title">Explore the unknown</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored3_body">Boredom is a call to explore. Open a book, a map, or your imagination!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored4_title">Challenge yourself</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored4_body">Set a small challenge for yourself and beat it. Excitement is around the corner!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored5_title">Every moment counts</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored5_body">Even quiet moments can be meaningful. Find something to appreciate right now.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored6_title">Try something exciting!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored6_body">Do something unexpected. Let boredom push you toward spontaneity!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored7_title">Learn a new skill</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored7_body">Use this time to grow! Pick up a skill you’ve always wanted to learn.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored8_title">Turn off autopilot</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored8_body">Boredom means you’re on autopilot. Switch things up and take control!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored9_title">Connect with someone</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored9_body">Reach out to a friend or family member. Conversations spark inspiration.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored10_title">Your inner artist awaits</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored10_body">Paint, draw, or write something. Creativity thrives in boredom!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored11_title">Revisit old dreams</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored11_body">Remember that hobby or dream you forgot about? Pick it back up!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored12_title">Go outside</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored12_body">Step into nature and let the fresh air renew your mind.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored13_title">Play like a kid</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored13_body">Do something funny and playful, like dancing or reading a book. Fun awaits!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored14_title">Write it out</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored14_body">Write about your boredom. You might discover what you truly want!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored15_title">Turn it into gratitude</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_bored15_body">Boredom means you have time to think. What are you grateful for today?</string>



    <!-- Sun Talk Restless -->
    <string name="sunTalk_restless1_title">Take some time</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless1_body">It\'s okay to feel this way. Take a deep breath, count to five, and remind yourself you are safe.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless2_title">You’ve got this</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless2_body">Anxiety doesn’t define you. You are stronger than this feeling, and it will pass.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless3_title">You’re not alone</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless3_body">Many people feel this way. It’s okay to reach out for help when needed.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless4_title">One step at a time</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless4_body">Focus on one thing at a time. You don’t have to solve everything right now.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless5_title">Title: It’s temporary</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless5_body">This feeling is temporary. You will overcome it, and always do so.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless6_title">Your inner calm</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless6_body">Inside you, there’s a place of calm. Close your eyes and try to find it.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless7_title">It’s okay to pause</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless7_body">Take a moment to pause and reset. Your well-being matters.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless8_title">Small wins matter</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless8_body">Celebrate small victories. Each one takes you closer to peace.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless9_title">Let it out</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless9_body">It’s okay to express your feelings. Cry, talk, or write. Release the tension.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless10_title">This is not for forever</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless10_body">Anxiety is a visitor, not a resident. It will leave in time.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless11_title">You’re brave</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless11_body">Facing anxiety takes courage. You’re doing better than you think.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless12_title">Feel your  surroundings</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless12_body">Focus on what you see, hear, and feel around you. Be present.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless13_title">It’s okay to be imperfect</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless13_body">Nobody’s perfect. It’s okay to feel anxious; it’s part of being human.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless14_title">You deserve peace</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_restless14_body">Peace is within reach. You’re allowed to rest and let go of worry.</string>




    <!-- Sun Talk happy -->
    <string name="sunTalk_happy1_title">Feel the joy!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy1_body">Happiness is contagious. Spread it everywhere you go!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy2_title">Life’s a gift</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy2_body">Every smile you wear is a little celebration of life.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy3_title">Be in the moment</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy3_body">Happiness isn’t in the future, it’s right here and now!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy4_title">Radiate positivity</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy4_body">A happy heart lights up the darkest days!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy5_title">Embrace the light</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy5_body">Happiness is not the absence of problems; it’s the strength to face them.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy6_title">Find your spark</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy6_body">Happiness often comes from within. Trust your inner light to guide you.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy7_title">Enjoy the ride</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy7_body">Happiness isn’t just a destination; it’s the journey.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy8_title">Feel your shine</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy8_body">Let the warmth of positivity brighten your day.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy9_title">Your joy is yours</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy9_body">No one can take your happiness away. It’s yours to keep!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy10_title">Heart full of smiles</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy10_body">Every smile is a step closer to a brighter tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy11_title">Let yourself shine</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy11_body">Your happiness inspires others. Share it freely!</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy12_title">Choose happiness</string>
    <string name="sunTalk_happy12_body">Each day offers a choice. Embrace the joy around you!</string>




    <!-- ChallengeHome -->
    <string name="Challenge_title">Specific tips and challenges</string>
    <string name="challenge_row1">Self-love</string>
    <string name="challenge_row2">Interacting with others</string>
    <string name="challenge_row3">Relaxation</string>
    <string name="challenge_column1">Breathing techniques</string>

    <!-- ProfileData -->
    <string name="profile_data_dateTitle">Date and title</string>
    <string name="profile_data_text">Text</string>
    <string name="profile_data_addB">Add</string>

    <!-- ChallengeChosenScreen -->
    <string name="challenge_emocional_type">Emotional</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_title1">Gratitude Practice</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_description1">Gratitude is a powerful emotional tool. Take a few minutes each day to reflect on the things you are grateful for. This can range from small things, like enjoying a cup of coffee, to significant achievements. Keeping a gratitude journal can help you focus on the positive and enhance your emotional well-being.</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_title2">Emotional Expression</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_description2">It’s essential to learn to express your emotions healthily. Talk to friends, family, or a therapist about how you feel. Open communication can help you process your emotions and reduce the emotional burden you may be experiencing.</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_title3">Mindfulness Practice</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_description3">Mindfulness allows you to be present in the moment, which can be very beneficial for your emotional health. Take time to meditate or simply breathe deeply. This will help you reduce anxiety and manage your emotions better.</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_title4">Establishing Limits</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_description4">Setting healthy boundaries is crucial for protecting your emotional well-being. Learn to say  &quot;no&quot; when something doesn\'t feel right. By doing so, you give yourself the necessary space to take care of yourself and avoid emotional burnout.</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_title5"> Regular Exercise</string>
    <string name="challenge_emocional_description5">Physical activity has a positive impact on your emotions. Exercise releases endorphins, known as &quot;happiness hormones.&quot; Try to incorporate at least 30 minutes of exercise into your daily routine, whether it\'s walking, doing yoga, or any activity you enjoy.</string>

    <string name="challenge_fisico_type">Health</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_title1">Maintain a Balanced Diet</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_description1">A balanced diet is essential for your physical health. Include a variety of foods: fruits, vegetables, lean proteins, whole grains, and healthy fats. Try to limit the intake of processed foods and added sugars. This will not only help you maintain a healthy weight but also provide you with the energy needed for your daily activities.</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_title2">Hydrate Properly</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_description2">Hydration is key for the optimal functioning of the body. Drink enough water throughout the day, especially if you are active or it\'s hot outside. Water helps regulate body temperature, transport nutrients, and eliminate waste. Try to carry a water bottle with you to remind yourself to drink regularly.</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_title3">Exercise Regularly</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_description3">Regular physical activity is fundamental for maintaining good physical health. Aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate exercise per week, such as walking, swimming, or cycling. Exercise not only improves cardiovascular health but also helps strengthen muscles and boost your mood.</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_title4">Get enough sleep</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_description4">Adequate sleep is crucial for both physical and mental health. Aim to sleep between 7 and 9 hours each night. Good rest helps your body recover, improves concentration, and regulates mood. Establishing a sleep routine can help you achieve better rest.</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_title5">Have Regular Medical Checkups</string>
    <string name="challenge_fisico_description5">Regular medical check-ups are important for detecting health issues early. Schedule annual check-ups and stay up to date with recommended vaccinations and screenings. This will allow you to address any health problems before they become more serious.</string>


    <string name="challenge_mental_type">Mental</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_title1">Practice Mindfulness</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_description1">Mindfulness involves being present in the current moment and recognizing your thoughts and feelings without judgment. Take time for meditation or breathing exercises. This practice can help reduce anxiety and stress, enhancing your emotional well-being.</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_title2">Maintain Social Connections</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_description2">Social connections are fundamental for mental health. Stay in touch with friends and family, and participate in community activities. Talking with others about your experiences can provide emotional support and a sense of belonging, which is crucial for your well-being.</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_title3">Establish Routines</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_description3">Having a daily routine can provide structure and predictability, which is beneficial for mental health. Try to set schedules for your daily activities, including time for work, relaxation, and exercise. This can help you feel more in control and reduce anxiety.</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_title4">Limit Exposure to Negative News</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_description4">Constant exposure to negative news can affect your mood and increase anxiety. Consider limiting your news and social media consumption. Instead, seek out sources of information that offer positive or inspiring stories to balance your perspective.</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_title5">Seek Professional Help</string>
    <string name="challenge_mental_description5">Don\'t hesitate to seek professional help if you feel that your mental health issues are overwhelming. Therapists and counselors are trained to help you develop strategies to manage your emotions and challenges. Seeking support is a sign of strength, not weakness.</string>

    <string name="challenge_espiri_type">Spiritual</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_title1">Practice Gratitude</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_description1">Gratitude is a powerful spiritual tool. By taking a moment each day to reflect on what you value in your life, you can elevate your spiritual energy and attract more positivity. Try keeping a gratitude journal where you note at least three things you are thankful for each day.</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_title2">Meditate Regularly</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_description2">Meditation is an essential practice for connecting with your inner self. Set aside time to sit in silence, focus on your breath, and let your thoughts flow without judgment. This not only reduces stress but also helps you find clarity and peace in your daily life.</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_title3">Connect with Nature</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_description3">Spending time outdoors can spiritually rejuvenate you. Nature has a healing effect that can help you reconnect with yourself and the world. Whether it\'s taking a walk in a park or simply sitting in your garden, allow the natural energy to envelop you.</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_title4">Set Intentions</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_description4">At the beginning of each day, take a moment to set your intentions. Ask yourself what you want to achieve and how you want to feel. By having clarity on your spiritual goals, you can direct your energy towards them and manifest positive changes in your life.</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_title5">Seek Community</string>
    <string name="challenge_espiri_description5">Surrounding yourself with people who share your spiritual interests can be transformative. Participate in meditation groups, workshops, or spiritual retreats. Connecting with others can provide support, inspiration, and new perspectives on your spiritual journey.</string>

    <!-- SunInputScreen -->
    <string name="sunInput_title">Write the title or date</string>
    <string name="sunInput_text">Tell me, how was your day?</string>
    <string name="sunInput_buttonSave">Save</string>
    <string name="sunInput_buttonCancel">Cancel</string>






</resources>